Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
One more, one more. Come on.
I just didn't expect
Shen Feng to like this type.
I think she's quite cute.
Can we roast tea over there?
Sure. I'll take you to have a look.
First,
gently touch the tea leaves.
Make sure every leaf gets heated.
Careful, the edges are hot.
How about I test her for you?
Let's see if she gets jealous.
Keep your eyes to yourself.
Stop finding fault with me.
Why are you so nervous?
You're so protective of her.
You won't even let her
shoot a video for me.
Hurry up.
Qingqing!
Are you going to learn or not?
I am.
Are you tired?
My sleeve accidentally
dragged in the water.
Can you help me roll it up?
Sure.
Let me help you.
Done.
My sleeve is wet too.
But I can roll it up myself.
Sorry,
I thought this plate needed to be washed.
It's okay. I'll clean it up.
It's okay. It's okay, Qingqing.
I don't need your help here.
Go get some rest.
Okay.
Then I'll go wipe the table.
Qingqing,
the ribs are almost done.
Have a taste.
Here.
Hot, hot, hot!
Spit it out, spit it out!
Are you okay?
Where did you get burned?
I'm fine.
I just need some water.
This time,
thank you all
for your great support of our event.
I'll finish my drink first.
Come on, cheers!
Cheers!
As the first experience officer
of this event,
I think Yunbianshang is really great.
It deserves to be known by more people.
When I go back,
I'll bring more friends here.
Thank you, A Jia.
Qingqing, we are friends now, right?
Good friends don't need to say thank you.
Then you must visit often in the future.
If your friends come,
I'll give them all a 50% discount.
I originally planned
to stay for just one day.
Now I don't want to leave at all.
Then don't leave.
I-I already booked your flight.
You should go back tomorrow.
Don't delay your work.
Are you that eager to see me leave?
But sorry,
I changed my itinerary.
I'm going to stay here
for a few more days.
Qingqing,
I'll have to trouble you
to take care of me from now on.
You're the one taking care of me.
Just remember
to give us more advice for Yunbianshang.
Qingqing, this shrimp is dead.
Let me peel a fresh one for you.
Nonsense.
I checked every single shrimp
on this plate
before cooking.
They were all alive and kicking.
Maybe I was wrong then.
Let me peel one for you.
I suddenly feel a bit crowded and cold.
Shu Rong, how about I sit with you?
Let's just eat.
What's going on
between A Jia and Shen Feng?
So this is the legendary bickering couple.
Eat some more.
This was supposed to be a relaxing trip.
Why does the itinerary include mountain
climbing and watching the sunrise?
Who on earth planned this?
Forget it. I'll stick it out.
Aren't you the tour leader?
Why are you at the very back?
I'm at the back
to prevent anyone from falling behind.
Let's go. Get in.
I'll drive you up.
We can drive up here?
Then why didn't you say so
last time we climbed the mountain?
Was it fun watching me exhaust myself?
My legs hurt for three days.
Last time was for a quest.
How could I let you complete it so easily?
I request to lower the quest difficulty,
or I'll delete my account and quit.
Request denied.
Let's go.
Zhe D 27F9A
Why didn't you go up
the mountain with Jia?
Why would I go up the mountain with her?
Don't you like her?
Even I can tell.
Every move you make is quite thoughtful.
But your temper isn't great.
You need to change that.
Playing hard to get is fun,
but sometimes it backfires.
I like her?
Jia is young, beautiful, and successful.
If you don't change your temper,
how will you win her heart?
Yun Qingqing,
sometimes I really want
to crack your head open like a walnut
to see if your brain is smooth.
I'm just trying to help.
Why are you insulting me?
Then, if I liked her,
you wouldn't be upset?
I'm not upset.
Why would I be upset?
Tell me,
am I a failure?
I've been the family role model
since I was little.
Everyone would praise me.
But look at me now.
I've worked so hard for so long,
but I have no car,
no house,
and no savings.
Why don't you comfort me?
Don't you know
I'm feeling terrible right now?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Say something. Why aren't you talking?
I'm really sad, okay?
Are you going to speak or not?
You're drunk.
Let's go.
Why are you...
Why won't it talk to me?
Be good. Don't move.
With your tolerance,
you still claim you never get drunk?
Come here.
Stop drinking. You've had too much.
It's cold in the mountains at night.
Don't catch a cold.
What's wrong?
You already have A Jia.
You can't treat other girls
like this anymore.
Otherwise, you're a jerk,
a player, and a flirt.
You care about her a lot.
I don't.
Do you want it?
Then answer my question.
You like her.
Actually, I'm a little bit upset.
But just a little bit.
Just a tiny bit.
Really.
I don't like her.
She's the real flirt.
She can fall for twelve guys
in ten minutes.
Don't be fooled.
This is a reward for your honesty.
It's mine now.
This puzzle piece is so pretty.
Do you see it?
Look at its shape.
I see it. Isn't it pretty?
Are you okay?
Last time...
was it on purpose?
Which time?
When your mouth
attacked my mouth.
Last time
was really an accident.
But this time can be intentional.